Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
[Whispers of Fate]
[همسات القدر]
[Episode 30]
[الحلقة 30]
If it weren't for that masked person
لو لم يكن ذلك الشخص المقنع
who sold me this rare medicine,
من باعني هذا الدواء النادر؟
I wouldn't have been able to return so early.
لم أكن لأتمكن من العودة مبكرا.
I'll go make the medicine to save Senior.
سأذهب لأصنع الدواء لإنقاذ الكبير.
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
Lici is absorbing Senior's power.
ليسي تمتص قوة كبار السن.
Lici!
وجه!
Let go.
اتركه.
Let go!
اتركه!
Let go now!
اتركه الآن!
♪ In dreams I drink and smile, half-drunk, half-awake ♪
♪ في الأحلام أشرب وأبتسم، نصف ثمل ونصف مستيقظ ♪
Fang Zhou.
فانغ تشو.
♪ As blossoms swirl around my qin ♪
♪ بينما تدور الأزهار حول تشين الخاص بي ♪
♪ Playing a tune in the forest ♪
♪ عزف لحن في الغابة ♪
♪ One cup of wine, one tear shed ♪
♪ كوب واحد من النبيذ، دمعة واحدة تذرف ♪
Fang Zhou.
فانغ تشو.
♪ Smoke fades into the sky ♪
♪ الدخان يتلاشى في السماء ♪
♪ Reflections flicker through the tower's haze ♪
♪ تنعكس الانعكاسات عبر ضباب البرج ♪
♪ My sleeve stained by dusk, I fish alone in autumn waters ♪
♪ كمي ملطخ بالغسق، أمارس الصيد وحدي في مياه الخريف ♪
Fang Zhou.
فانغ تشو.
Wake up, Fang Zhou.
استيقظ، فانغ تشو.
♪ Fallen leaves return ♪
♪ عودة الأوراق المتساقطة ♪
Wake up, Fang Zhou!
استيقظ، فانغ تشو!
♪ When will I? ♪
♪ متى سأفعل؟ ♪
♪ A lifetime isn't enough ♪
♪العمر لا يكفي ♪
♪ To carve you into my heart ♪
♪ لنحتك في قلبي ♪
♪ Clouds roll by my fluttering robe ♪
♪ تتدحرج السحب بجانب ردائي المرفرف ♪
Fang Zhou.
فانغ تشو.
♪ For whom do I dance again? ♪
♪ لمن أرقص مرة أخرى؟ ♪
Get up!
استيقظ!
♪ Under these skies, stars fall like rain ♪
♪ تحت هذه السماء، تتساقط النجوم مثل المطر ♪
Say something.
قل شيئا.
♪ One heart, one path, one dream ♪
♪ قلب واحد، طريق واحد، حلم واحد ♪
Say something!
قل شيئا!
♪ All too fleeting ♪
♪ كلها عابرة للغاية ♪
♪ I hold the mountains and rivers close in flowing moonlight ♪
♪ أحتضن الجبال والأنهار في ضوء القمر المتدفق ♪
♪ Toasting away all love and hate ♪
♪ نخب كل الحب والكراهية ♪
You promised me
لقد وعدتني
that you would survive.
أنك سوف تنجو.
♪ Wishes granted or lost to emptiness ♪
♪ الأمنيات التي تحققت أو ضاعت بسبب الفراغ ♪
Fang Zhou!
فانغ تشو!
♪ One thought, one vow, one life ♪
♪ فكرة واحدة، عهد واحد، حياة واحدة ♪
Fang Zhou.
فانغ تشو.
♪ I drink in the wind ♪
♪ أنا أشرب في الريح ♪
♪ Cross the mortal dust through bloom and decay ♪
♪ عبور الغبار البشري من خلال الإزهار والتحلل ♪
♪ When the final note fades ♪
♪ عندما تتلاشى النغمة الأخيرة ♪
♪ Only sighs remain for each reunion ♪
♪ لا يبقى إلا التنهدات لكل لقاء ♪
No.
لا.
♪ Autumn wind stirs ♪
♪ رياح الخريف تهب ♪
♪ Rain falls without mercy ♪
♪ يهطل المطر بلا رحمة ♪
No.
لا.
♪ Flowers bloom, wither, and scatter ♪
♪ تتفتح الزهور وتذبل وتنتشر ♪
♪ Petals drift through the sky to greet me ♪
♪ بتلات الزهور تطير عبر السماء لتحييني ♪
♪ The farewell song hides in my heart ♪
♪ أغنية الوداع تختبئ في قلبي ♪
♪ Becoming the poem I never finished ♪
♪ أصبحت القصيدة التي لم أكملها أبدًا ♪
♪ Grace may fade, but this journey was not in vain ♪
♪ قد تتلاشى النعمة، لكن هذه الرحلة لم تذهب سدى ♪
Wait.
انتظر.
♪ One heart, one path, one dream ♪
♪ قلب واحد، طريق واحد، حلم واحد ♪
♪ All too fleeting ♪
♪ كلها عابرة للغاية ♪
There's another way.
هناك طريقة اخرى
♪ I hold the mountains and rivers close in flowing moonlight ♪
♪ أحتضن الجبال والأنهار في ضوء القمر المتدفق ♪
There's another way to save you.
هناك طريقة أخرى لإنقاذك.
♪ Toasting away all love and hate ♪
♪ نخب كل الحب والكراهية ♪
♪ Wishes granted or lost to emptiness ♪
♪ الأمنيات التي تحققت أو ضاعت بسبب الفراغ ♪
Lie down first.
استلقي أولاً.
♪ One thought, one vow, one life ♪
♪ فكرة واحدة، عهد واحد، حياة واحدة ♪
♪ I drink in the wind ♪
♪ أنا أشرب في الريح ♪
♪ Cross the mortal dust through bloom and decay ♪
♪ عبور الغبار البشري من خلال الإزهار والتحلل ♪
♪ When the final note fades ♪
♪ عندما تتلاشى النغمة الأخيرة ♪
♪ Only sighs remain for each reunion ♪
♪ لا يبقى إلا التنهدات لكل لقاء ♪
♪ Once seen the vast sea, no other waters compare ♪
♪ بمجرد رؤية البحر الواسع، لا توجد مياه أخرى تقارن به ♪
♪ With broken wings, I still fly like a black bird ♪
♪ بأجنحة مكسورة، ما زلت أطير مثل طائر أسود ♪
♪ Clouds drift apart, why stay lost in dreams? ♪
♪ تتباعد الغيوم، لماذا نبقى ضائعين في الأحلام؟ ♪
♪ The past is gone, its blade now a tombstone ♪
♪ لقد مضى الماضي، وأصبح نصله الآن شاهد قبر ♪
♪ I've severed the last of my obsession's shadow ♪
♪ لقد قطعت آخر ظل هوسي ♪
♪ Ask not of joy or sorrow ♪
♪ لا تسأل عن الفرح أو الحزن ♪
♪ Regret not, nor repent ♪
♪ لا تندم ولا تتوب ♪
♪ One heart, one path, one dream ♪
♪ قلب واحد، طريق واحد، حلم واحد ♪
♪ Calm and steady ♪
♪ هادئ وثابت ♪
♪ Writing my colors across eternity ♪
♪ أكتب ألواني عبر الأبدية ♪
♪ Toasting away all love and hate ♪
♪ نخب كل الحب والكراهية ♪
♪ Wishes granted or lost to emptiness ♪
♪ الأمنيات التي تحققت أو ضاعت بسبب الفراغ ♪
Monster!
وحش!
♪ One thought, one vow, one life ♪
♪ فكرة واحدة، عهد واحد، حياة واحدة ♪
♪ From the heart ♪
♪ من القلب ♪
♪ I laugh at all the heroes ♪
♪ أنا أضحك على جميع الأبطال ♪
♪ When the final note fades ♪
♪ عندما تتلاشى النغمة الأخيرة ♪
♪ Kindred spirits ♪
♪ أرواح متقاربة ♪
♪ Need no reunion ♪
♪ لا حاجة إلى لم شمل ♪
♪ The qin's notes linger on ♪
♪ ملاحظات تشين لا تزال مستمرة ♪
♪ The jade flute echoes afar ♪
♪ صدى الناي اليشم يتردد من بعيد ♪
♪ Like the loveliest smile within a dream ♪
♪ مثل أجمل ابتسامة في الحلم ♪
♪ Do you know? ♪
♪ هل تعلم؟ ♪
♪ Can you tell? ♪
♪ هل يمكنك أن تقول؟ ♪
♪ Rebirth and return are just echoes lost in mist ♪
♪ الولادة الجديدة والعودة مجرد صدى ضائع في الضباب ♪
Sleep peacefully.
نم بسلام.
Wait for me…
الانتظار لي…
to bring you back to life.
لإعادتك إلى الحياة.
You're here.
أنت هنا.
I thought…
اعتقدت…
you were dead.
لقد كنت ميتا.
Didn't you say
ألم تقل؟
I was trouble?
لقد كنت مشكلة؟
Trouble
مشكلة
doesn't die so easily.
لا يموت بسهولة.
I've always told myself
لقد قلت لنفسي دائما
not to believe what you say.
لا أصدق ما تقول.
I really hate you.
أنا أكرهك حقا.
I hated you from the beginning,
لقد كرهتك منذ البداية
and at the end,
وفي النهاية،
I still hate you.
لا أزال أكرهك.
What about in between?
ماذا عن بينهما؟
In between, I didn't hate you as much.
بينما أنا لم أكرهك كثيراً.
Lici.
وجوه.
I'm jealous of you.
أنا غيور منك.
Because I'm more powerful than you?
لأنني أقوى منك؟
Because despite how dangerous you were,
لأنه على الرغم من مدى خطورتك،
Fang Zhou still chose to trust you,
لا يزال فانغ تشو يختار أن يثق بك،
passing the Heart-Moon Return to you,
مرورًا بعودة قلب القمر إليك،
and Zhoudi Tower as well.
وبرج زهودي أيضًا.
What about me?
ماذا عني؟
I was here long before you.
لقد كنت هنا قبل وقت طويل.
What was I to him?
ماذا كنت بالنسبة له؟
You were a good junior to him
لقد كنت صغيرا جيدا بالنسبة له
and a bad senior to me.
وكبير سيء بالنسبة لي.
Actually,
في الحقيقة،
he knew I was hiding something.
لقد علم أنني أخفي شيئًا ما.
Yet he still chose to believe in me.
ومع ذلك فإنه اختار أن يؤمن بي.
But I
ولكن انا
couldn't bring myself
لم أستطع أن أحمل نفسي
to trust Shei from the beginning.
أن أثق في شيي منذ البداية.
Shei?
شي؟
Hao Wenhou's fiancée?
خطيبة هاو وين هو؟
I originally thought
اعتقدت في الأصل
you sent her to me.
لقد أرسلتها لي.
Why would I send someone
لماذا أرسل شخص ما؟
with no martial arts skills
بدون مهارات فنون القتال
to you?
لك؟
Then why did Fang Zhou trust me?
إذن لماذا وثق بي فانغ تشو؟
Because that's just how he was.
لأنه هكذا كان.
He clearly knew
لقد كان يعلم بوضوح
about your connection
حول اتصالك
with Yique Yinyang.
مع ييكي ينيانغ.
Yet he still believed he could guide you properly.
ومع ذلك فهو لا يزال يعتقد أنه قادر على إرشادك بشكل صحيح.
Only he could do that.
هو فقط من يستطيع فعل ذلك.
I couldn't.
لم أستطع.
And you
وأنت
couldn't either.
لا أستطيع أيضًا.
Did he really love every single person
هل كان يحب كل شخص حقًا؟
in this world that much?
في هذا العالم إلى هذا الحد؟
He would
هو سوف يفعل
sacrifice himself for someone
يضحي بنفسه من أجل شخص ما
he'd never even met.
لم يلتق به قط.
How foolish.
كم هو أحمق.
I think so too.
أعتقد ذلك أيضًا.
I told him that.
لقد قلت له ذلك.
But he wouldn't listen.
ولكنه لم يستمع.
One time,
مرة واحدة،
he brought an injured tiger from the mountain
أحضر نمرًا مصابًا من الجبل
back to Zhoudi Tower for treatment.
العودة إلى برج زهودي لتلقي العلاج.
It scared away all the children
لقد أخافت جميع الأطفال
living in the peach blossom forest.
العيش في غابة أزهار الخوخ.
Fu had to feed the tiger.
كان على فو أن يطعم النمر.
When the tiger roared,
عندما زأر النمر،
he was scared half to death.
لقد كان خائفا حتى الموت.
Any news about Fu?
هل هناك أي أخبار عن فو؟
I've been looking for him too.
لقد كنت أبحث عنه أيضاً.
I miss Fu's cooking.
أفتقد طبخ فو.
Indeed.
بالفعل.
Where can we find a chef
أين يمكننا العثور على طاهٍ؟
who masters cuisines from nine provinces?
من يتقن مأكولات تسعة محافظات؟
So,
لذا،
whenever I arrive at a new place,
كلما وصلت إلى مكان جديد،
I visit the famous local restaurants
أقوم بزيارة المطاعم المحلية الشهيرة
to taste their food.
لتذوق طعامهم.
If Fu really became a chef,
إذا أصبح فو طاهيًا حقًا،
his restaurant
مطعمه
would certainly be
سيكون بالتأكيد
the most famous one in the area.
الأكثر شهرة في المنطقة.
Fu's cooking—
طبخ فو—
I could recognize it with just one bite.
أستطيع التعرف عليه من خلال قضمة واحدة فقط.
Perhaps
ربما
while eating around,
أثناء تناول الطعام حولها،
I'll eventually find him.
سأجده في نهاية المطاف.
Me too.
أنا أيضاً.
Lici,
وجوه،
I've searched,
لقد بحثت
but Fang Zhou's body isn't here.
لكن جسد فانغ تشو ليس هنا.
You said you'd prove it to me,
لقد قلت أنك سوف تثبت لي ذلك،
and I'll trust you
وسوف أثق بك
one last time.
مرة أخيرة.
Follow me.
اتبعني.
[Fang Zhou's Tomb]
[قبر فانغ تشو]
This is the cenotaph I built for him.
هذا هو النصب التذكاري الذي بنيته له.
His body isn't inside.
جسده ليس بالداخل.
I know.
أنا أعرف.
Above this tomb,
فوق هذا القبر،
I've set up a formation of the Tianren Realm.
لقد قمت بتشكيل تشكيل لمملكة تيانرين.
Ordinary people can't see through it,
الناس العاديون لا يستطيعون الرؤية من خلاله،
so it can protect Fang Zhou.
حتى يتمكن من حماية فانغ تشو.
If what you say is true,
إذا كان ما تقوله صحيحا،
I'll return the power of the Rebirth Scroll
سأعيد قوة مخطوطة الميلاد الجديد
to you.
لك.
This formation
هذا التشكيل
changes with the flow of time.
تتغير مع تدفق الوقت.
Every day,
كل يوم،
the hour
الساعة
and direction
والاتجاه
to open the formation change accordingly.
لفتح تشكيل التغيير وفقا لذلك.
Even on the same day,
حتى في نفس اليوم،
the position to open the formation differs.
يختلف موقف فتح التشكيل.
From the position of the one opening the formation,
من موقع الشخص الذي يفتح التشكيل،
the moon
القمر
must be
يجب أن يكون
directly above the cenotaph.
فوق النصب التذكاري مباشرة.
If you miss the time,
إذا فاتك الوقت،
you cannot
لا يمكنك
open it again that day.
افتحه مرة أخرى في نفس اليوم.
Besides,
بجانب،
opening the formation
فتح التشكيل
also requires the power of the bone-washing silver bracelet.
يتطلب أيضًا قوة سوار غسل العظام الفضي.
Senior.
كبير.
I've made an agreement with Shui Duopo.
لقد توصلت إلى اتفاق مع شوي دوبو.
As long as you return the power of the Rebirth Scroll
طالما أنك تعيد قوة مخطوطة إعادة الميلاد
to me,
لي،
she will extract from my abdomen
ستستخرجه من بطني
Fang Zhou's heart crystal
بلورة قلب فانغ تشو
to help resurrect him.
لمساعدته على إحيائه.
I want to see him again.
أريد أن أراه مرة أخرى.
May I?
ربما أنا؟
Yes,
نعم،
but not for too long.
ولكن ليس لفترة طويلة.
Yan.
نعم.
We need to seal the coffin now.
نحن بحاجة إلى إغلاق التابوت الآن.
I keep telling myself
أنا أظل أقول لنفسي
not to be deceived by you.
لا أنخدع بك.
But I still can't help
ولكنني لا أزال غير قادر على المساعدة
believing you again and again.
أصدقك مرارا وتكرارا.
Now,
الآن،
you're trying to fool me
أنت تحاول خداعي
with such a cheap trick,
مع هذه الحيلة الرخيصة،
and you still expect me to believe you?
ومازلت تتوقع مني أن أصدقك؟
What are you talking about?
ماذا تتحدث عنه؟
How could this be?
كيف يمكن أن يكون هذا؟
It's impossible.
إنه مستحيل.
How could this happen?
كيف يمكن أن يحدث هذا؟
Where is Fang Zhou?
أين فانغ تشو؟
Tang Lici,
تانغ ليكي,
you're still acting even now!
أنت لا تزال تمثل حتى الآن!
How could this happen?
كيف يمكن أن يحدث هذا؟
Where exactly is Fang Zhou?
أين يقع فانغ تشو بالضبط؟
Where is he?
أين هو؟
Where exactly is he?
أين هو بالضبط؟
Fang Zhou's been dead for years!
لقد مات فانغ تشو منذ سنوات!
He died at Zhoudi Tower four years ago!
لقد توفي في برج زهودي منذ أربع سنوات!
His body was never found!
لم يتم العثور على جثته أبدًا!
Tang Lici.
تانغ ليكي.
Don't try to fool me again!
لا تحاول خداعي مرة أخرى!
Liu Yan.
ليو يان.
Did you tell Ghostly Peony
هل أخبرت شبح الفاوانيا؟
about Fang Zhou?
عن فانغ تشو؟
Do you take me for a fool?
هل تظنني أحمق؟
I didn't tell anyone
لم أخبر أحدا
about Fang Zhou!
حول فانغ تشو!
So you do know him.
إذن أنت تعرفه.
Has Ghostly Peony
لديه الفاوانيا الشبحية
ever been to Zhoudi Tower?
هل سبق لك زيارة برج Zhoudi؟
You just said it yourself.
لقد قلت ذلك بنفسك.
This is a formation of the Tianren Realm.
هذا هو تشكيل عالم تيانرين.
Without the bone-washing silver bracelet,
بدون سوار الفضة لغسل العظام،
no one can open it.
لا أحد يستطيع فتحه.
He did come here,
لقد جاء هنا
but he couldn't do anything!
ولكنه لم يستطع فعل أي شيء!
Ghostly Peony is Yique Yinyang!
الفاوانيا الشبحية هي ييكي ينيانغ!
Yeah.
نعم.
Ghostly Peony is Yique Yinyang.
الفاوانيا الشبحية هي ييكي ينيانغ.
Why didn't I realize this sooner?
لماذا لم أدرك هذا عاجلا؟
He's not merely the vessel
إنه ليس مجرد وعاء
for Yique Yinyang's spirit.
لروح Yique Yinyang.
He's Yique Yinyang himself!
إنه Yique Yinyang نفسه!
Otherwise…
خلاف ذلك…
how could he open the formation?
كيف استطاع أن يفتح التشكيل؟
Impossible.
مستحيل.
Impossible!
مستحيل!
Shut up!
اسكت!
No, you shut up!
لا، اسكت!
Liu Yan.
ليو يان.
Listen to me.
استمع لي.
Ghostly Peony has stolen
لقد سرق الفاوانيا الشبحية
Fang Zhou's body.
جسد فانغ تشو.
Let's join forces
دعونا نجمع قوانا
to make him return
لإعادته
Fang Zhou's body.
جسد فانغ تشو.
Tang Lici, you're really something.
تانغ ليسي، أنت حقا شيء مميز.
How can you tell one lie
كيف يمكنك أن تقول كذبة واحدة
after another?
بعد الآخر؟
Liu Yan!
ليو يان!
Shut up!
اسكت!
Fine.
بخير.
You won't help me.
لن تساعدني
Then I'll do it myself.
ثم سأفعل ذلك بنفسي.
Tell me.
أخبرني.
Where is Ghostly Peony?
أين يوجد نبات الفاوانيا الشبحية؟
After I kill you,
بعد أن أقتلك،
I'll send him to see you.
سأرسله لرؤيتك.
Liu Yan.
ليو يان.
I'm asking you one more time.
أنا أسألك مرة أخرى.
Where is
أين هو
Ghostly Peony?
الفاوانيا الشبحية؟
Yan!
الذي - التي!
Don't go!
لا تذهب!
Yan.
نعم.
Fang Zhou.
فانغ تشو.
Ghostly Peony.
الفاوانيا الشبحية.
Ghostly Peony!
الفاوانيا الشبحية!
Tang Lici will definitely not let you go.
تانغ ليسي لن يسمح لك بالرحيل بالتأكيد.
The formation of the Tianren Realm
تشكيل مملكة تيانرن
required the bone-washing silver bracelet as the key.
كان مطلوبًا سوار غسيل العظام الفضي كمفتاح.
Fortunately, Qiaoyi Qiankun made it in time.
لحسن الحظ، وصل Qiaoyi Qiankun في الوقت المناسب.
That was close,
كان ذلك قريبا
wasn't it?
أليس كذلك؟
Fang Zhou's body is missing.
جثة فانغ تشو مفقودة.
Do you think
هل تعتقد
Tang Lici can still remain calm?
هل لا يزال بإمكان تانغ ليسي أن يظل هادئًا؟
At least,
على الأقل،
Liu Yan can't stay calm.
ليو يان لا يستطيع البقاء هادئا.
Lies attract more lies.
الأكاذيب تجذب المزيد من الأكاذيب.
Around one lie,
حول كذبة واحدة،
there are at least four more.
هناك أربعة آخرين على الأقل.
Fang Pingzhai's Inverted Dream.
حلم فانغ بينجزاي المقلوب.
Fang Zhou's body at Zhoudi Tower.
جسد فانغ تشو في برج تشودي.
Around Tang Lici,
حول تانغ ليسي،
how many more lies are there?
كم عدد الكذبات المتبقية؟
Head Fang,
ناب الرأس،
I can't persuade your disciple.
لا أستطيع إقناع تلميذك.
I just hope that when you learn your resurrection
أتمنى فقط أنه عندما تتعلم قيامتك
was paid for
تم الدفع مقابل
with your disciple's life,
مع حياة تلميذك،
you won't blame me.
لن تلومني.
Miss Shei.
السيدة شي.
Senior.
كبير.
Mr. Tang has been gone for days.
لقد ذهب السيد تانغ منذ أيام.
Do you know where he went?
هل تعلم أين ذهب؟
He's not my responsibility.
إنه ليس مسؤوليتي.
Besides,
بجانب،
that fox
هذا الثعلب
must be plotting something.
لا بد من التخطيط لشيء ما.
He might be
ربما يكون
stirring up trouble somewhere.
إثارة المشاكل في مكان ما.
You talk
انت تتحدث
just like Chi.
تمامًا مثل تشي.
Do I?
هل افعل؟
I told you he's cunning.
لقد قلت لك أنه ماكر.
This is
هذا هو
Head Fang's figurine?
تمثال رئيس فانغ؟
You know it?
هل تعلم ذلك؟
I've seen it before.
لقد رأيته من قبل.
Mr. Tang has been carving it recently.
لقد قام السيد تانغ بنحته مؤخرًا.
I didn't expect
لم اتوقع
he'd finish it so quickly.
سوف ينهي الأمر بسرعة كبيرة.
His face...
وجهه...
Shei.
شي.
Brother.
أخ.
My sister Fang Ci
أختي فانغ سي
is now in your care.
هو الآن في رعايتك.
I must go to the mountain to learn skills
يجب أن أذهب إلى الجبل لتعلم المهارات
to fight against Yique Yinyang.
للقتال ضد ييكي ينيانغ.
I don't know if I'll survive.
لا أعلم إذا كنت سأنجو.
Her past name no longer matters.
لم يعد اسمها السابق مهما.
From now on, call her Shei.
من الآن فصاعدا، اسميها شي.
Father.
أب.
Your brother's name is
اسم أخيك هو
Fang Zhou.
فانغ تشو.
He's been looking for you.
لقد كان يبحث عنك.
Brother.
أخ.
It's me.
هذا أنا.
Brother, where are you?
أخي أين أنت؟
Brother!
أخ!
He's Tang Lici.
إنه تانغ ليسي.
Do you want revenge?
هل تريد الانتقام؟
With your memory intact,
مع ذاكرتك سليمة،
you can't fool Tang Lici.
لا يمكنك خداع تانغ ليسي.
Have you lost your memory before?
هل فقدت ذاكرتك من قبل؟
What?
ماذا؟
I used the Xuluo needle
لقد استخدمت إبرة Xuluo
to pierce your Yuzhen acupoint.
لاختراق نقطة الوخز بالإبر الخاصة بك في Yuzhen.
You had no reaction.
لم يكن لديك أي رد فعل.
This is a symptom of memory loss.
وهذا أحد أعراض فقدان الذاكرة.
Forget your brother.
انسى أخاك
Miss Shei,
السيدة شي،
you confuse me.
أنت تربكني.
You're in this game,
أنت في هذه اللعبة
yet you know
ولكنك تعلم
nothing about it.
لا شيء عنه.
Miss Shei.
السيدة شي.
Miss Shei, what's wrong?
آنسة شي، ما الأمر؟
Shei?
شي؟
Fang Zhou is gone.
لقد رحل فانغ تشو.
He really died because of me.
لقد مات حقا بسببي.
Master!
يتقن!
I need to complete the final refinement
أحتاج إلى إكمال التحسين النهائي
of the Thousand Curse Needle.
من إبرة اللعنة الألف.
Get out!
اخرج!
No.
لا.
To refine the Thousand Curse Needle,
لتكرير إبرة اللعنة الألف،
you must force it out through the Tianmen acupoint.
يجب عليك إخراجه من خلال نقطة الوخز بالإبر في تيانمن.
The pain will kill you.
الألم سوف يقتلك.
If Tang Lici isn't dead yet,
إذا لم يكن تانغ ليسي ميتًا بعد،
how can I die?
كيف يمكنني أن أموت؟
Master.
يتقن.
Tang Lici
تانغ ليزي
isn't worth you suffering like this.
لا يستحق الأمر أن تعاني مثل هذا.
Master!
يتقن!
Don't tell me what to do!
لا تخبرني ماذا أفعل!
Get out!
اخرج!
Master!
يتقن!
Open the door!
افتح الباب!
Tang Lici.
تانغ ليكي.
I'll make you wish you were dead.
سأجعلك تتمنى الموت.
I'll make you wish you were dead!
سأجعلك تتمنى الموت!
Mr. Tang,
السيد تانغ،
reports from the front:
تقارير من الجبهة:
Xifang Tao has gathered troops on the western front.
وقد جمع شيفانغ تاو قواته على الجبهة الغربية.
Fucui is on the eastern side.
فوكوي تقع على الجانب الشرقي.
It seems they plan
يبدو أنهم يخططون
to strike from both sides
الضرب من كلا الجانبين
to attack the Sword Alliance.
لمهاجمة تحالف السيف.
They're determined to fight
إنهم مصممون على القتال
to the death with the Alliance.
حتى الموت مع التحالف.
Master Shao,
المعلم شاو،
any news of Ghostly Peony?
هل هناك أي أخبار عن Ghostly Peony؟
Not yet,
ليس بعد،
but Fengliu Shop has mobilized all their forces this time.
لكن متجر فنغليو حشد كل قواته هذه المرة.
Ghostly Peony will certainly come.
سوف يأتي الفاوانيا الشبح بالتأكيد.
Tongsha River and Xiulao Peak
نهر تونغشا وقمة شيولاو
on the east and west of Mount Cloud
على شرق وغرب جبل كلاود
are crucial for gaining
ضرورية لتحقيق
the upper hand against the Alliance.
اليد العليا ضد التحالف.
Mr. Tang,
السيد تانغ،
do you have a strategy?
هل لديك استراتيجية؟
At this moment,
في هذه اللحظة،
neither side has fully recovered its strength.
ولم يتمكن أي من الجانبين من استعادة قوته بالكامل .
Fengliu Shop has sent out all their forces
لقد أرسل متجر فنغليو كل قواته
because they want a quick victory.
لأنهم يريدون انتصارًا سريعًا.
With this battle,
مع هذه المعركة،
they aim to determine the winner between them and us.
هدفهم هو تحديد الفائز بينهم وبيننا.
The Tongsha River forms a natural barrier to the west.
يشكل نهر تونغشا حاجزًا طبيعيًا إلى الغرب.
The banks on both sides are flat.
البنوك على كلا الجانبين مسطحة.
Liu Yan will deploy the Nine Qilin Transformations
سوف يقوم ليو يان بنشر تحولات تشيلين التسعة
there.
هناك.
We can position our main forces along the river.
يمكننا وضع قواتنا الرئيسية على طول النهر.
Master Puzhu and I
أنا والمعلم بوزو
will lead the Sword Alliance
سيقود تحالف السيف
and the Yanmen disciples to fight them.
وتلاميذ يانمن لمحاربتهم.
On the east side,
على الجانب الشرقي،
at Xiulao Peak,
في قمة شيولاو،
we can take advantage of the mountain
يمكننا الاستفادة من الجبل
and maintain a strong defense.
والحفاظ على دفاع قوي.
Master Shao,
المعلم شاو،
you and Master Cheng
أنت والسيد تشنغ
should establish a defensive line here together.
ينبغي علينا إنشاء خط دفاعي هنا معًا.
Hold your ground without attacking.
حافظ على موقعك دون الهجوم.
Once Master Puzhu and I
ذات مرة، أنا والسيد بوزو
break through the western line together,
اختراق الخط الغربي معًا،
we'll move downstream along the river
سنتحرك باتجاه مجرى النهر
and circle behind Fucui
ودائرة خلف فوكوي
to attack from both the front and back.
للهجوم من الأمام والخلف.
Fengliu Shop
متجر فنغليو
will be annihilated in this one battle.
سيتم القضاء عليهم في هذه المعركة الواحدة.
If Liu Yan makes a move…
إذا قام ليو يان بالتحرك...
Even if he doesn't come for me,
حتى لو لم يأتي لي،
I'll go after him.
سأذهب خلفه.
Master.
يتقن.
All troops are in position.
جميع القوات في مواقعها.
We await your command.
نحن في انتظار أمرك.
Starting tomorrow,
ابتداء من الغد،
gather all our forces
جمع كل قواتنا
to completely destroy the Sword Alliance.
لتدمير تحالف السيف بالكامل.
Notify Qiaoyi Qiankun
إخطار تشياويي تشيانكون
to act as the vanguard
للعمل كطليعة
and break through the front line at the Tongsha River.
واختراق الخطوط الأمامية عند نهر تونغشا.
Qingchan,
كينغشان
you will assist Palace Chief Xifang.
سوف تقوم بمساعدة رئيس القصر Xifang.
The battle at Tongsha River
معركة نهر تونغشا
can't be lost!
لا يمكن أن تضيع!
Yes, Master.
نعم سيدي.
Fucui,
فوكوي،
I'm giving you the remaining
أنا أعطيك الباقي
Blood Ghost Pills.
حبوب شبح الدم.
Xiulao Peak's terrain is complex.
تعتبر تضاريس قمة شيولاو معقدة.
You'll have to fight on foot.
سوف يتوجب عليك القتال سيرًا على الأقدام.
Bring Kuanglan Wuxing
أحضر كوانغلان ووكسينغ
with you.
معك.
Yes.
نعم.
Then, Master,
ثم يا سيدي،
which front will you lead?
إلى أي جبهة ستقود؟
Wherever Tang Lici is,
أينما كان تانغ ليسي،
that's where I'll be.
هذا هو المكان الذي سأكون فيه.
Set off now.
إنطلق الآن.
Don't worry, Mr. Chi.
لا تقلق يا سيد تشي.
With Yanmeng here,
مع يانمينج هنا،
they won't be able to cross
لن يتمكنوا من العبور
the Tongsha River.
نهر تونغشا.
Tongsha—
تونغشا—
what a good name.
ما اسم جيد.
Let's kill
دعونا نقتل
every last one of them right here.
كل واحد منهم هنا.
Mr. Tang.
السيد تانغ.
Have you found Ghostly Peony yet?
هل وجدت Ghostly Peony بعد؟
Ten li southwest
Ten li southwest
lies Master Puzhu's unit.
تقع وحدة السيد بوزو.
All of you stay here.
جميعكم ابقوا هنا.
I'll go to help them.
سأذهب لمساعدتهم.
Shen.
شين.
Have you noticed that Foxy Tang has been
هل لاحظت أن فوكسي تانج كان
acting stranger and stranger lately?
هل أصبح التصرف غريبًا وغريبًا في الآونة الأخيرة؟
I'll go check.
سأذهب للتحقق.
Ants!
النمل!
You're all just ants!
أنتم جميعا مجرد نمل!
What kind of monster is that?
ما نوع هذا الوحش؟
Nine Qilin Transformations!
تسعة تحولات تشيلين!
Run!
يجري!
Light Technique.
تقنية الضوء.
Unbreakable Snare!
فخ غير قابل للكسر!
Don't kill him!
لا تقتله!
Take him as a hostage.
أخذه كرهينة.
Where is Ghostly Peony?
أين يوجد نبات الفاوانيا الشبحية؟
That's not something I should know.
هذا ليس شيئاً ينبغي لي أن أعرفه.
Only one of you needs to live.
واحد فقط منكم يحتاج للعيش.
Let's see which one that'll be.
دعونا نرى أي واحد سيكون.
You're not escaping.
أنت لا تهرب.
Step aside!
تنحى!
Puzhu's wounded!
بوزو جريح!
Not my problem.
ليست مشكلتي.
Tang Lici!
تانغ لي!
How could you lose
كيف يمكن أن تخسر؟
your usual composure?
رباطة جأشك المعتادة؟
That fire was poisonous.
كانت تلك النار سامة.
Return to camp and rest.
العودة إلى المخيم والراحة.
The fire poison is fierce.
السم الناري شرس.
Master Puzhu,
المعلم بوزو،
you must return to the Sword Alliance
يجب عليك العودة إلى تحالف السيف
and seek treatment from Shui Duopo.
وطلب العلاج من شوي دوبو.
We're in the middle
نحن في المنتصف
of a decisive battle with Fengliu Shop.
من معركة حاسمة مع متجر فنغليو.
I can't retreat now.
لا أستطيع التراجع الآن.
Going into battle wounded
الذهاب إلى المعركة جريحًا
will only aggravate the injury.
لن يؤدي إلا إلى تفاقم الإصابة.
Then, Mr. Tang,
ثم السيد تانغ،
can you stay calm?
هل تستطيع أن تبقى هادئا؟
Why do you ask?
لماذا تسأل؟
I've
لقد
never seen you
لم اراك من قبل
so angry before.
كنت غاضبا جدا من قبل.
I know what I'm doing.
أنا أعرف ما أفعله.
Xifang Tao, what are you doing here?
شيفانغ تاو، ماذا تفعل هنا؟
I'm just here to deliver medicine.
أنا هنا فقط لتوصيل الدواء.
Why don't you two believe me?
لماذا لا تصدقوني؟
A cat delivering rice to a mouse—
قطة تقدم الأرز للفأر
who'd buy that?
من سيشتري هذا؟
How is Master Puzhu?
كيف حال المعلم بوزو؟
If you came to spy on our forces,
إذا أتيت للتجسس على قواتنا،
you'll have to leave some intel
سيتعين عليك ترك بعض المعلومات
before you go.
قبل أن تذهب.
This medicine
هذا الدواء
won't fully neutralize the fire poison,
لن يتم تحييد سم النار بشكل كامل،
but it can ease
ولكن يمكن أن يخفف
Master Puzhu's pain for now.
ألم المعلم بوزو في الوقت الراهن.
No one here believes that.
لا أحد هنا يصدق ذلك.
I do.
أفعل.
Miss Tao,
الآنسة تاو،
did you bring this medicine
هل احضرت هذا الدواء
especially for me?
خاصة بالنسبة لي؟
As you can see.
كما ترون.
May I leave now?
هل يمكنني أن أغادر الآن؟
Since you're already here,
بما أنك هنا بالفعل،
why leave?
لماذا تغادر؟
Sir,
سيد،
don't forget
لا تنسى
that we stand on opposite sides.
أننا نقف على الجانبين المتقابلين.
If that's the case,
إذا كان الأمر كذلك،
why
لماذا
save me at all?
أنقذني على الإطلاق؟
I'm indebted to you.
أنا مدين لك.
I wanted to offer myself to you,
أردت أن أقدم نفسي لك،
but I feared you'd refuse,
ولكنني كنت خائفة من أن ترفض،
so all I could give was this antidote.
لذلك كل ما أستطيع أن أقدمه هو هذا الترياق.
They're...
إنهم...
Is your tongue broken?
هل لسانك مكسور؟
There's nothing improper between Master Puzhu and me.
لا يوجد شيء غير لائق بيني وبين السيد بوزو.
Besides,
بجانب،
he's the successor of Tianjing Pavilion—
إنه خليفة جناح تيانجين
he's as chaste as they come.
إنه عفيف تمامًا.
Foxy Tang,
فوكسي تانغ،
are you just letting her go?
هل أنت فقط تسمح لها بالرحيل؟
If Ghostly Peony dies,
إذا ماتت زهرة الفاوانيا الشبحية،
will you
سوف تفعل
be free again?
أن تكون حرا مرة أخرى؟
Where is
أين هو
Ghostly Peony?
الفاوانيا الشبحية؟
If you'd asked me earlier,
لو سألتني في وقت سابق،
I'd have told you
كنت سأخبرك
he was at Plum Garden.
كان في حديقة البرقوق.
But a few days ago,
ولكن قبل بضعة أيام،
he somehow
هو بطريقة ما
got hold of a coffin.
حصلت على نعش.
A coffin?
نعش؟
He said he was going to
قال أنه سوف يذهب
the Sky-Ascending Pillars in Puti Valley.
أعمدة السماء الصاعدة في وادي بوتي.
The Sky-Ascending Pillars built by Yique Yinyang?
أعمدة السماء الصاعدة التي بناها ييكي ينيانغ؟
I guess
اعتقد
he wants to place
يريد أن يضع
that coffin there.
هذا التابوت هناك.
Can we trust you?
هل يمكننا أن نثق بك؟
You won't get more from me even if you kill me.
لن تحصل على المزيد مني حتى لو قتلتني.
At least we can't let you remain a threat.
على الأقل لا يمكننا أن نسمح لك بالبقاء تهديدًا.
Mr. Tang,
السيد تانغ،
isn't this repaying kindness with enmity?
أليس هذا هو رد الجميل بالعداوة؟
Because of your sneak attack,
بسبب هجومك المتسلل،
Master Puzhu was injured.
لقد أصيب المعلم بوزو.
You brought him medicine
لقد أحضرت له الدواء
because you owed him a favor.
لأنك مدين له بمعروف.
And this strike of mine
وهذه إصابتي
was for your ambush just now.
كان لكمينك الآن.
For seven days,
لمدة سبعة أيام،
you'll only have 30% of your power,
سيكون لديك 30% فقط من قوتك،
but it won't be life-threatening.
لكنها لن تشكل تهديدا للحياة.
This settlement
هذه التسوية
is more than merciful.
هو أكثر من رحيم.
Mr. Tang, you're quite calculating.
السيد تانغ، أنت حاسب جيدا.
This is indeed fair.
وهذا عادل بالفعل.
Master Puzhu,
المعلم بوزو،
farewell.
وداع.
Why did she only say
لماذا قالت فقط
farewell to you?
وداعا لك؟
Master Puzhu,
المعلم بوزو،
your injuries are severe,
إصاباتك خطيرة
but if you return to the Sword Alliance,
ولكن إذا عدت إلى تحالف السيف،
Shui Duopo can heal you.
يمكن لـ Shui Duopo أن يشفيك.
You can return to battle within seven days.
يمكنك العودة إلى المعركة خلال سبعة أيام.
That's faster than
هذا أسرع من
Miss Xifang's
الآنسة شيفانغ
recovery time.
وقت التعافي.
Also,
أيضًا،
please notify Her Highness quickly
يرجى إبلاغ صاحبة السمو بسرعة
to send reinforcements to Tongsha River.
لإرسال تعزيزات إلى نهر تونغشا.
Ideally,
من الناحية المثالية،
General Yuchi
الجنرال يوتشي
should personally command the troops.
ينبغي أن يتولى قيادة القوات شخصيا.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
I will return to the Alliance immediately.
سأعود إلى التحالف على الفور.
Thank you, Master Puzhu.
شكرا لك، سيد بوزو.
Tang Lici.
تانغ ليكي.
I have something to say.
عندي شيء أريد قوله.
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
The coffin
التابوت
and your strange behavior.
وسلوكك الغريب
Fang Zhou…
فانغ تشو ...
is not dead.
ليس ميتا.
Fang Zhou isn't dead?
فانغ تشو ليس ميتًا؟
That's impossible.
هذا مستحيل.
Why is it impossible?
لماذا هذا مستحيل؟
When Fang Zhou
عندما فانغ تشو
had just a breath left,
لم يتبقَّ سوى أنفاس قليلة،
I extracted his heart crystal with my own hands
لقد استخرجت بلورة قلبه بيدي
and buried it in my abdomen.
ودفنته في بطني.
With my self-healing constitution,
مع دستوري القادر على الشفاء الذاتي،
I've been nurturing this heart crystal,
لقد كنت أعتني ببلورة القلب هذه،
cleansing the evil energy
تطهير الطاقة الشريرة
left by Yique Yinyang.
غادر بواسطة Yique Yinyang.
That's why
لهذا السبب
you've been having stomach pains.
لقد كنت تعاني من آلام في المعدة.
Does Liu Yan know?
هل يعرف ليو يان؟
He doesn't believe me.
إنه لا يصدقني.
You're truly insane.
أنت مجنون حقا.